Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Audio
  - Subseries A: Audio, 1776-1785
    - Funkadelic I, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0318)
      Side B: Cosmic Slop, [Track Unknown], Nappy Dugout, You Can't Miss, Red Hot Mamma, Alice in My Fantasies, Sexy Ways, Standing on the Verge, Comin' Round the Mountain, If You Got Funk
    - Afrika Bambaata '81/Grand Wizard Theodore, 1981 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0319)
      Side A: Afrika Bambaata '81
      Side B: Grand Wizard Theodore
    - N.W.A.: Straight Outta Compton, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0320)
      Side A: Straight Outta Compton, _ _ _ _ Tha Police, Gangsta Gangsta, If It Ain't Ruff, Parental Discretion iz Advised, 8 Ball (Remix), Something Like That
      Side B: Express Yourself, Compton's n The House (Remix), I Ain't Tha 1, Dopeman (Remix), Quiet on Tha Set, Something 2 Dance 2
      Container Annotation: ©1988 Priority Records/Ruthless Records. Commercial Release
    - REV, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0321)
    - Beastie Boys Pass the Mic [EP], undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0322)
      Sides A and B: Pass the Mic (LP version), Jimmy James (LP version), Dub the Mic, Drunken Praying Mantiss Style, Pass the Mic pt. 2 (Skills to Pay the Bills), Jimmy James (instrumental), Netty's Girl.
    - Jumping Master, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0323)
    - Rebel Radio, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0324)
    - DUB CLUB BAD PARTY - Ragamuffin Style, Sambo, First Blood, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0325)
      Container Annotation: 132 W 20 St WED NT. 1am
    - Nuf Respect to Odoc, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0326)
    - Warrior, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0327)
    - Reggae 86, 1986 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0328)
    - Ragamuffin 88, 1988 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0329)
    - Reggae 89, 1989 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0330)
    - Killer Hurts, 1982 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0331)
      D1on -> Rockin Well, CCC, To the Depths of Hell, '82. [image on container]
    - 51 Storm, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0332)
    - Rankin, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0333)
    - Dread at the Control 4, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0334)
    - Dread at the Control 3, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0336)
    - Stereograph Live. London '80, Peter., 1980 (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0337)
      Side A: Sound System
    - Body Music, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0338)
    - Revolution Sounds - Big Youth, undated (Box 6, Media ID: 213.0339)
      Side A (Revolution Sounds): Burning Spear - Travelin'; Fred Locks - Black Starliner
      Side B: Revolution Sounds - Big Youth
    - Bowie Interview Nov. 28, 1975, November 28, 1975 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0340)
      Side A: (Handwritten over printing, See Container Annotation) "Bowie Interview Nov. 28th 1975"
      Container Annotation: How Media Will Be Judged and Bought in 1975, Highlights of the 5th Annual Media Decisions Seminar. © 1975 The Martin S. Fliesler Company. Commercial Release
    - Public Image Ltd., Orpheum Theatre Boston, 1, April 18, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0341)
      Side A: Careering, Annalisa, Attack, Poptones, Low Life, Public Image, Death Disco
      Side B: Bad Baby, Home is Where the Heart is, Theme, Chant; Another, Public Image, Memories, Poptones
    - Public Image Ltd., NYC Palladium April 20 1980, 2 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0342)
      Side A: Intro, Careering, Annalisa; Attack, Low Life, Fodderstompf, Death Disco, Memories, Public Image
      Side B: Another, Poptones
    - Public Image Ltd., NYC April 22nd, 1980, Great Gildersleeves, 3, April 22, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0343)
      Side A: Chant, Public Image, Attack, Another, Low Life, Bad Baby, Memories, Fodderstompf, Public Image
      Side B: Careering, Annalisa, Poptunes, Chant
    - Public Image Ltd., Phil April 26, '80, April 26, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0344)
    - Public Image Ltd., Staten Island, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0345)
    - Public Image Ltd., Orpheum Auditorium L.A., 9, May 4, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0346)
      Side A: Intro, Careering, Annalisa, Low Life, Chant, Death, Poptones
      Side B: Religion, Bad Baby, Public Image, Memories, Russia with Love
    - Public Image Ltd., San Francisco May 10th 1980, South Market Cultural Center, 10, May 10, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0347)
      Side A: Intro, Careering, Annalisa, Attack, Low Life, Chant, Death Disco
      Side B: Poptones
    - Palladium Check April 20th/Great Gildersleeves, April 20, [no year] (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0348)
    - Public Image Ltd., Brooklyn Zoo, January 29, 1983 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0349)
      Side A: Blue Water, Where Are You, Annalisa, Bad Baby, Careering, Religion, Home is Where…, Theme, Swan Lake, Chant
      Side B: Attack, Mad Max, Public Image, Low Life;, No Birds, Under the House
    - Sex Pistols, Anarchy in the USA, Dallas Jan 10, 1978/San Francisco Jan 14, 1978 Winterland -Radio-, January 10, 1978/January 14, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0350)
      Side A: God Save the Queen, Wanna Belle, Seventeen, NY, EMI, Bodies, Belsen was a Gas, Holidays in the Sun, No Feelings, Problems, Prett Vacant
      Side B: Anarchy in the USA, No Fun, God Save the Queen, Wanna Be Me, Seventeen, NY, EMI, Belson was a Gas, Bodies
    - De La Soul - Buhloone Mindstate/ Gumbo - Dropping Soulful, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0351)
      Side A: "De La Soul Buhloone Mind State"
      Side B: "Gumbo"
    - Pistols - The Feelies Dec 14, 1977 CBGB, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0352)
      Contents
      Side A: Anarchy, Seventeen, N.Y., Steppin Stone, Satellite Submission, Liar, No Feeling, Substitute, Pretty Vacant, Problems, No Fun
      Side B: No Fun, Substitute, Pretty Vacant, Problems, Did You, No Wrong, Pushin Shovin, Seventeen, Sid on Trial
    - Sex Pistols - Atlanta 1/5/78, January 5, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0353)
      Side A: God Save the Queen, I Wanna Be Me, Seventeen (I'm a Lazy Sod), New York, Bodies, Submission, Holidays in the Sun
      Side B: EMI, No Feelings, Problems, Pretty Vacant, Anarchy in the UK/+ Iggy Stooge: TV Eye/I Feel Alright!!
    - Feelies Max's (one set) 21 May/CBGB (late show) 2 July 1978, May 21, 1978/July 2, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0402)
      Side A: Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Loveless Love, Fever, Work, Original Love, Crazy, Moscow Nights
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl$, Raised, Crazy Rhythms
    - Hell, CBGB, Thursday Late June 21st '79 Master/ Feelies, Club 57 June 23 '79 Copy, June 21, 1979/June 23, 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0403)
      Side A: Kid, Crack of Dawn, I Live My Life, I'm Goin, Crosstown Traffic, Lowest Common Denominator, Ignore That Door
      Side B: unknown
    - The Feelies 6.14.78 Max's, June 14, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0404)
      Side A: Boy Next Door, Moscow Nights, Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl, Original Love, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Mosow Nights, Work, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms, Lookin at You
    - Feelies Hurrah March 15, '79/Happy Spring March 21st '79 CBGB, March 15, 1979/March 21, 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0405)
      Side A: Boy, Original Love, Work, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythm, I'm a Believer, Lookin at You
      Side B: Boy, Original Love, Work, Loveless Love, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Raised Eyebrows -->Crazy Rhythms, I'm a Believer
    - Feelies CBGB 22 July '78, July 22, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0406)
      Side A: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Work, Original Love, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Work, Loveless Love (crossed out), Clean Girl, Original Love, Raised Eye--> Crazy, Looking at You
      Container Annotation: Greg Delazio - percussion
    - Slits, Irving Plaza Club 57, Nov 15th 1980, November 15, 1980 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0267)
      Side A: Newtown, Walkabout, Grapevine, Life on Earth, Man Next Door, Typical Girls, Fade Away, Animal Space.
      Side B: Silence is a Rhythm, Shake
    - Iggy My Father's Place Nov. 4, 1979;John Cale Sabotage/Live (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0407)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, [Track Unknown], I'm Loose, Dogfood, New Valves, T.V. Eye, Sixteen, Your Pretty Face, Play It Safe, Funtime, Be Your Dog-->
      Side B: (Cont'd), China Girl/ Cale: Mercenaries (Ready For War), Baby You Know, Evidence, Dr. Mudd, Only Time Will Tell, Sabotage
    - Iggy & the Stooges, 1969 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0408)
      Side A: I Wanna Be Your Dog, No Fun, Real Cool Time, Not Right, Little Doll, Down on the Street, Loose, T.V. Eye, Dirt, 1970
      Side B: Funhouse, Search & Destroy, Your Pretty Face is Going to Hell, Raw Power, Shake Appeal, Death Trip
    - Iggy Pop Live March 18th 1977, March 18, 1977 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0409)
      Side A: Raw Power, T.V. Eye, Dirt, 1969, Turn Blue, Funtime, Gimmie Danger, No Fun, Search & Destroy, I Wanna Be Your Dog
      Side B: Tonight, Some Weird Sin, China Girl
      Container Annotation: Iggy w/ P.S. Group - 96 Tears
    - The Feelies Dec 14, 1977 CBGB, December 14, 1977 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0410)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La, Clean Girl, Work, [Track Unknown], Little Red Book, Moscow Night, Crazy Rhythms
      Side B: Boy Next Door, Original Love/Sin, Third Uncle, The Thin Line, [Track Unknown], Work, Moscow Night, Slippin
    - Some Jams NYC 78 Speed, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0411)
      Side A: Jam: Richard Lloyd and the Feelies Max's Kansas City NYC / 19 Jan 78 Side 1 of 2 (45:54)
      Side B: Side 2 of 2 Patti Smith Group, Richard Lloyd, Richard Hell "My Generation" CBGBs II / NYC 31 Dec 77, 1 Jan 78 (8:52)// Hurram Jam / Hurrahs NYC / 4 Sept 78 John Cale, Chris Spedding, T. Taliafero Drummer (20:47)
      Container Annotation: © Performances and All Original Material Copyright 1978 By the Artists. All Commercial Rights Retained
    - Richard & Linda Thompson Sept 7th Round House London, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0412)
      Contents: (Original text crossed out, See Container Annotation for Original Text)
      Side B: Jet Plane in a Rocking Chair(), Never Again*, For Shame of Doing Wrong(), Hokey Pokey+, Looking for You*/Steeleye Span (T.V.) Ballad of Robin Hood, One Misty Musty Morn, Spotted Cow
      Container Annotation: Advertising Age 7th Annual Idea Workshop Consumer Direct Mail
    - Iggy Pop Oct 31, '79 Palladium, October 31, 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0414)
      Side A: Real Cool Time, [Track Unknown], I'm Loose, Dog Food, New Values, T.V. Eye, Sixteen, Pretty Face Going to Hell, Play It Safe
      Side B: Funtime, [Track Unknown], I Wanna Be Your Dog, China Girl, One For My Baby An' One Forthe Road, No Fun, Five Foot One, [Track Unknown]
    - MC5 Lester Bangs Saginaw Auditorium, Demo, January 1, 1970 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0414)
      Side A: Ramblin Rose, Human Being Lawnmower, Tonight, Rocket Reducer #62, It's a Man's World, Teenage Lust, Looking at You, Five of Love, Shakin' Street, Starship-->, Kickout the Jams
      Side B: I Sold My Babe, Let it Blurt
      Container Annotation: [J.D. Dougherty] - Drums, Bob [Quinel] - Guitar
    - Madness TR3, Sunday Nov 25 '79, November 25, 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0415)
    - B-52's, Talking Heads, Aug 16. '79 Central Park, August 16, 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0416)
      Side A: Planet Claire, Big Country
      Side B: Warning Sign, Building On Fire, Book I Read, Paper, [Track Unknown], Stay Hungry, [Track Unknown]
    - Talking Heads Live, Assorted Dates, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0417)
      Side A: Girls Wanna Be w/ the Girls, With Our Love, Psycho Killer, I'm Not in Love (cut), Building on Fire, Artist's Only, Warning Sign, No Compassion, Artists Only, First Week/Last Week, ...With Our Love
      Side B: Love is Like a Building on Fire, Who is it?, Thank You For Sending Me An Angel, Book I Read, Don't Worry About Gov't, Psycho Killer, Building On Fire, Thank You For Sending Me An Angel, Stay Hungry, [Track Unknown], 96 Tears
      Container Annotation: Tracks 1-8: Live at CBGB July 18, 1975; Tracks 9-14: Live at Max's May 19, 1976; Tracks 15-22: Live at Max's Oct 8th, 1976; Tracks 23-25 Live at CBGB Jan 25, 1976
    - Talking Heads CBGB Sunday August 28th 1977. "Voidoids Village Gate Friday August 26th 77" (crossed out), August 28, 1977 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0418)
      Side A: Love-->Building on Fire, Love Comes to Town, Don't Worry About the Gov't, Take Me to the River, Don't Take My Love Away, Pulled Up, No Compassion
      Side B: Love Comes to Town, With Our Love, Girls w/ Girls, Tentative Decisions, Thank You For --> Angel, Who is it?, I'm Not In Love, Love-->Building, Psycho Killer, Love is All Around
    - Talking Heads CBGB 3-Piece Band, 1976 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0419)
      Side A: Artists Only, ...Book I Read, Happy Day, Don't Worry...Government, Thank you...an Angel, Last Week...Carefree, Buildings on Fire, New Feeling, I'm Not In Love, Girls Want 2 B w/ tha Goils!!!
      Side B: With Our Love, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That!!!, Psycho Killa, Tentative Decisions, Stay Hungry, Warning Sign, Who Is It?, Love is All Around, 1-2-3-Red Light
    - Early TV Video Dub Spring 74?/Talking Heads Summer 75 Video Dub, One Plus One, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0420)
      Contents: Merry Christmas + Cassette Luv to Peter
      Side A: Double Exposure, Change Your Channel, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Venus de Milo, [Track Unknown], Sympathy for the Devil
      Side B: Girls Wanna Be w/ the Girls, With Our Love, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That, I'm Not In Love, Psycho Killer, Warning Sign, Pablo Picasso*, Oh Oh I Love Her So (Blondie)
      Container Annotation: T.V. Early 1974 w/ R. Hell - bass, vocal; Live at CBGB's Summer 1975 (Aug 15th), *10/9/76
    - Blondie CBGB July 18, 1975, CBGB Aug 1975, CBGB May 7, 1978, 1975, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0421)
      Side A: Little Girl Lies, In the Flesh, Moonlight, Drive, Charlotte Harlot, Platinum Blonde, Man Overboard, Little Girl Lies, In the Still of the Night, Femme Fatale, Sweet Lulabye
      Side B: Sister Midnight, Denise
    - Nervus Rex May 26 Max's/B-52's June 1 '78 CBGB, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0422)
      Side A: Index, I Love You or Whatever, Love Affair, Fun w/ Numbers, No Regrets, Sort of, Rachel in the Ruins [?], Don't Look at Me That Way/She Came From Planet, Hero Worship, 52 Girls, Devin in My Car
      Side B: Downtown, Rock Lobster, Hero Worship, 52-Girls, Devils in My Car, Downtown, Lava, Runnin Around
    - B-52's Sat Late Sept 23, 1978 CBGB/Hurrah Oct 1 '78 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0423)
      Side A: 52 Girls, Hero Worship, Devil's in my Car, Downtown, Moon in the Sky, Dance, Rock Lobster, Runnin' Around
      Side B: Planet Cloud, Hero Worship, 52 Girls, Devil's in my Car, Downtown, [Track Unknown], Lava, Moon in the Sky..., [Track Unknown]
    - B-52's September 21, 1978 CBGB (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0424)
      Side A: She Came From Planet Cloud, Dance, Runnin' Around, Downtown, Lava, There's a Moon, Strobe Light, Rock Lobster
      Side B: 52 Girls, Hero Worship, devin's in My Car, Downtown, Running Around, Dance, Rock Lobster, Strobe Light
    - Heartbreakers ala Book, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0425)
    - JT [Thunders], unknown (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0426)
    - The Cramps Live June 10th 1977, Nov 4th CBGB, Dec 13, 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0427)
      Side A: The Way I Walk, Love Me, Domino, What's Behind the Mask, Don't Eat Stuff off the Sidewalk, Teenage Werewolf, Sunglasses After Dark, I Put You in My TV Set, Human Fly, [Strinne] Love Me, Domino, What's Behind the Mask
      Side B: Jungle Hop, Teenage Werewolf, Sunglasses After Dark, I'm Cramped, T.V. Set, Surfin' Bird, Human Fly, What Color Panties Are Ya Wearing?, Daddy Drives a UFO
    - DEVO Max's 5-25-77, A Grape Tape, Plus Iggy 1, May 25, 1977 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0428)
      Side A: Human Race, Social Fools, Be Stiff, Too Much Paranoias, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Spud Boy, Sloppy, Satisfaction, Blockhead, Soo Bawlz, Penetration in the Centerfold
      Side B: Mongoloid, Gut Feeling, Jocko Homo, Come Back Johnny, Words Get Stuck in My Throat, [Track Unknown], That's How Strong My Love Is-->FAME, I Wanna Be Your Dog
    - Erasers/Feelies/Cramps/CBGBS/Live/NYC 77/78, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0429)
      Contents: CBGBs/LIVE/NEW YORK CITY
      Side A (The Erasers 29 May 77/Set 2 (28:16); The Feelies 29 May 77/Set1 Side 1 of 2 (16:59)): Jody, No Fun, Funtime, Come out in the Streets, Marc in Leather, Everybody's Got a Dog, I Don't Love Anyone, Boy Next Door, Fa Ce La
      Side B (The Feelies (Cont) Side 2 of 2 (12:49); The Cramps 19 Feb 78/Set 2 (29:44)): I'm a Believer, Original Love, Human Fly, Love Me, What's Behind the Mask, Jungle Hop, Teenage Werewolf, Daddy, Drives a UFO, Strycnine, What Color Panties? Hanky Panky, Surfin Bird
      Container Annotation: Performances and All Material Copyright 1977 and 1978 by the Artists. All Commercial Rights Reserved.
    - Cramps 8-18-79 WPIX Dolby/Undertones 9-20-79 Palladium, 1979 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0430)
      Side A: CRAMPS 8-18-79 11:03-11:43pm WPIX
      Side B: True Confessions, Girls Don't Like It, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Billy's Third, [Track Unknown], Jump Boys
    - Contortions/Cramps CBGB Fri April 14th 1978 late show, April 14, 1978 (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0431)
      Side A: My Infatuation, I Got a Roving Eye, Love Twice Removed, Throw Me Away, Flip Your Face, Jaded But So in Love
      Side B: The Way I Walk, Love Me, Jungle Hop, Human Fly, [S+rec], I'm Cramped, Hanky Panky
    - Hip Hop Junkies Vol. IV, Puffin On a Blunt!, Alex Baby: Straight Outta Ronin! In Tha Mix!, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0432)
      Side A: Alex Baby
      Side B: "How High?"
    - Rocket From the Tombs '75 w/ Peter Laughner, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 213.0433)
      Sides A and B: Intro, I'm 18
    - Feelies September 78 - Max's Sept 1, 1978 Early/Max's Sept 2, 1978 Early, September 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0434)
      Side A: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights,... Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl, Original Love, Raised Eyebrows--> Crazy Rhythms --> Well Alright
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, ...Work, Loveless Love, Clean Girl-->Original Love, Raised Eyebrows-->Crazy Rhythms, Well Alright
    - Sid Vicious Max's Sept 8, 1978 w/ Mick Jones, J. Nolan, A. Kane & S. Doir, September 8, 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0435)
      Side A: DEVO 10-14-78, Search and Destroy, I Wanna Be Your Dog, Pushin & Shovin', Something Else, Belsen was a Gas, Steppin Stone, Chinese Rocks, My Way, [Track Unknown]
      Container Annotation: Side A: 1, 2, 5, 3/Side B: 3 cont'd, 4,6,7,9
    - Devo 76 Studio Demos - Talking Heads Demos, 1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0436)
      Side A: (Devo) Sloppy, Blockhead, Uncontrollable Urge, Secret Agent Man, Clock-Out, Auto Mowdown, Smart Patrol, Mechanical Man, Be Stiff, Bottled Up/ (Talking Heads) First Week/Last Week..., Artists Only, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That
      Side B: New Feeling*, Book I Read*, Not in Love*, Love-->Building, Book I Read, I'm Not in Love, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That
      Container Annotation: *Live
    - Devo Mabuhay Tapes, Aug 3, '77, Sept 12, '77, 1977 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0437)
      Side A: Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoia, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Smart Patrol/Mr DNA, Gut Feeling, Sloppy, Jocko Homo, Clock Out
      Side B: Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoia, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Jocko Homo, Smart Patrol-Mr DNA, Gut Feeling, Sloppy, The Words Get Stuck in My Throat
    - Undertones Hurrah Sept 23 '79 plus WPIX, September 23, 1979 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0438)
      Side A: Here Comes the Summer
    - Deadline CBGB Nov 29th, 1980/Elodie Lawton [Wednesday] March 4th 1981 Max's, November 29, 1980, March 4, 1981 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0439)
      Contents: Unknown
    - Cuban Heels July 26th 1977 CBGB/Nervus Rex Tuesday October 18 1977 CBGB (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0440)
      Side A: Come Out in the Streets, Time To Wake Up, I Remember, [Track Unknown], Joey Run Run, [Track Unknown], California, Secret Agent
      Side B: (Fun with numbers*), Third Word, Duplicate, Love Affair, Index, I Love You or Whatever, [Track Unknown], 1250, Rachel in Ruins Again, December Pledge
      Container Annotation: *Soundcheck, Miriam, Trixie, [Sham]
    - Talking Heads Entermedia Theater August 10, 1978 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0441)
      Side A: No Compassion, Warning Sign, Book I Read, Girls w/ the Girls, Love Comes to Town, With Our Love, Love--> Building
      Side B: I Found a Job, Electricity, Big Country, Pulled Up
    - Talking Heads 3/13/76, Talking Heads Dec 7th, 1975 CBGB Set I, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0442)
      Sides A and B: (Talking Heads March 13, 1976) Love is All Around; 1,2,3, Redlight; 96 Tears/(December 7th 1975), Girls Wanna Be with the Girls, First Week/Last Week, Artists Only, Building on Fire, With Our Love, Warning Sign II, Psycho Killer, Tentative Decisions, I Wanna Live, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That, I'm Not in Love, Stay Hungry, Girls w/Girls (crossed out), With Our Love (crossed out), I Wish You Wouldn't Say That (crossed out), So in Love
    - Talking Heads Central Park '80 Dr. Pepper, August 27, 1980 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0443)
      Side A: Psycho Killer, Warning Sign, Stay Hungry, Cities, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown]
      Side B: Crosseyed & Painless, Life During Wartime, Take Me to the River, [Track Unknown]
    - Talking Heads July 29, 1976 CBGB, STEREO Set #1/Talking Heads Set #2 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0444)
      Side A: Artists Only ([gone]), Don't Worry About Gov't, Love is All Around, Building on Fire, Who is it?, Thank You For Sending Me An Angel, ...With Our Love, Book I Read
      Side B: Girls w/ Girls, Happy Feeling, Stay Hungry, New Feeling, I'm Not in Love, Warning Sign
    - Iggy Pop Suckcess Tour, Hunt & Tony Sales, A Grape Tape, October 6, 1977 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0445)
      Side A: Sixteen, Lust for Life, Neighborhood Threat, The Passenger, I Gotta Right
      Side B: Some Weird Sin, Nightclubbin, Raw Power, That's How Strong My Love Is
    - Heads cont'd, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0446)
      Side A: Artists Only, Psycho Killer, Life During Wartime, Take Me to the River, No Compas[sion], Designed to Kill, Throw Me Away
    - Talking Heads T.V. Aug 3 Last show with Lloyd -almost-Thanks/Roxy Music Oct 18th, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0447)
      Side A (Talking Heads, TV 8/3): Girls Wanna Be With Girls, With Our Love, Psycho Killer, Tentative Decision/(T.V.) Fire Engine, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel
      Side B (Roxy Music): Street Life, Remake/ReModel, Do the Strand, Re-Make, Editions of You, Do the Strand, -encores-, Thrill of it All, Hard Rains Gonna Fall
    - Stooges Live '74, 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0448)
      Side A: Raw Power, Rich bitch, Wet My Bed, I Got Nothin', Cock in My Pocket, Search & Destroy, Gimmie Danger
      Side B: I Got Nothin'
    - MTV EMA 30 Sec 1st Demo, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0449)
    - New York Dolls, Montreal, Canada 27.9.74, September 27, 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0450)
      Side A: Lookin For A Kiss, Who Are the Mystery Girls, Something Else, Pills, Give Her A Great Big Kiss, Subway, It's Too Late
      Side B: Trash, Bad Girl, Chatterbox, Puss in Boots, Stranded in the Jungle
    - Newsrap, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0451)
      Side A: "Newsrap" - M.T.V; Rough Guide Demo 1) with Drumloop 2) without Drumloop, 130 B.P.M.
      Container Annotation: Dan Denovan 289.3484
    - MTV Ident: Clive Walley Demo for Peter Dougherty, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0452)
    - MTV Rough Demo, undated (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0453)
      Sides A and B: MTV Awards 60 Secs, MTV Awards 30 Secs, For Demo Only, Barry Adamson
    - VH1 15/6/94, June 15, 1994 (Box 8, Media ID: 213.0454)
      Contents: VH1 Revised Ideas